<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>white crime on WeStopCrime.com</title>
    <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/tags/white-crime/</link>
    <description>Recent content in white crime on WeStopCrime.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://WeStopCrime.com/tags/white-crime/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SOPHISTIZATION AND ANONYMIZATION OF THE FINANCIAL FRAUD CRAFT</title>
      <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/2019/05/25/financial-fraud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WeStopCrime.com/2019/05/25/financial-fraud/</guid>
      <description>SOPHISTIZATION AND ANONYMIZATION OF THE FINANCIAL FRAUD CRAFT In general, we can say that different degrees of enlightenment, ranging from lying claims over deception to real enlightenment, have long existed in a primal form, but in the meantime highly refined forms have also crystallised. The latter are mainly found in financial fraud, for example in certain life settlements and in certain interest rate swaps. Certain excrescences are even so sophisticated that they are, as it were, almost &amp;lsquo;predestined&amp;rsquo; to mislead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FINANCIAL CRIMES TO MANKIND</title>
      <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/2018/05/22/financial-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WeStopCrime.com/2018/05/22/financial-crime/</guid>
      <description>FINANCIAL CRIMES TO MANKIND: TOO BIG FOR JAIL? Today there are large-scale investigations into the manipulation of the price of gold. In Europe, the United States and Asia, an investigation is also underway into banks operating on an international level that are suspected of manipulating exchange rates on a large scale. The European Commission suspects some of the largest investment banks in the world of having made agreements to shield the market of credit default swaps from competitors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>