<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tops on WeStopCrime.com</title>
    <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tops on WeStopCrime.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://WeStopCrime.com/top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/about/</guid>
      <description>Jeffrey J McGee Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Jeffrey J McGee, struggling for a better society. I have been working in the anti financial fraud unit for over 25 years now. I consider it as my mission on this planet to detect financial fraud and make sure that even the big fish pay their taxes. This is my blog where I share my insights to the world. I hope you enjoy it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/books/</guid>
      <description>Financial Shenanigans, Fourth Edition: How to Detect Accounting Gimmicks and Fraud in Financial Reports by Howard Schilit , Jeremy Perler , et al. | Mar 28, 2018
Anatomy of a Fraud Investigation: From Detection to Prosecution by Stephen Pedneault | Feb 8, 2010
Money Laundering Prevention: Deterring, Detecting, and Resolving Financial Fraud by Jonathan E. Turner | Jun 7, 2011</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/write-for-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://WeStopCrime.com/top/write-for-us/</guid>
      <description>As you may have noticed, on our wrime website, the blog section still is very active. If you are searching for a guest post publication, containing fresh content of criminality related research or ideas to give our visitors a nice read, you may as well read on.
On our blog, we try to publish contributions with the latest scientific criminiality report news, the very best insights and new trends and world of crime and legal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>